mining.com 2006-06-15

# InfoMine - The Internet's Premier Mining Information Site

### Privacy Policy

Effective November 9, 2000

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it accessible from virtually every page on InfoMine. 

**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all personal information collected or submitted by clients when they subscribe, advertise or purchase products on InfoMine. The types of personal information collected are: 

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email address 
  * Phone number 
  * Credit/Debit Card Information 

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to keep you informed of new developments at InfoMine which we believe would be of interest to you. We do not share these addresses with outside parties. We use information posted in the automated email inquiry forms on our listings to confirm the contact email for the listing and validate inquires generated from our site. We do not share this contact information with anyone except the recipient listed on the contact form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our subscription form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us and requesting it. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at +1 604 683-2037 or send us an email at [info@infomine.com](mailto:info@infomine.com).
